{
    "subject": "resource/Vadim_Pisarev",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Dance",
    "human_readable": "Vadim Pisarev's occupation is dance.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9329743981361389,
            "question": "Is Vadim Pisarev a dancer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9034911394119263,
            "question": "Describe Vadim Pisarev's occupation."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.851044774055481,
            "question": "What is Vadim Pisarev's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6187996864318848,
            "question": "What is Vadim Pisarev's chosen career path?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6109367609024048,
            "question": "What is Vadim Pisarev's area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5980761647224426,
            "question": "What is the primary activity that Vadim Pisarev engages in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4244743883609772,
            "question": "What type of work is Vadim Pisarev known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3584655225276947,
            "question": "How would you describe Vadim Pisarev's line of work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34717902541160583,
            "question": "What does Vadim Pisarev do for a living?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3220667243003845,
            "question": "What kind of art form does Vadim Pisarev practice?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vadim Pisarev's occupation is dance.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6846_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does Vadim Pisarev do for a living?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6846_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe Vadim Pisarev's line of work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6846_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work is Vadim Pisarev known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6846_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6846_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6846_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6846_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6846_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6846_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6846_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6846_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6846_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6846_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6846_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents provide several references to Vadim Pisarev's profession and career. Specifically, the document from file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6846/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt states: \"Vadim pisarev is a famous Ukrainian dancer...\" This information suggests that Vadim Pisarev's occupation is indeed dance."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide extensive information about Vadim Pisarev, describing his career as a dancer. They mention his training in ballet, his performances, and the numerous awards he received in the field of dance. This information supports the statement that Vadim Pisarev's occupation is dance."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}